ip-tracker.org 2018-10-28

# Privacy Policy | IP-Tracker.org

### Cookies

Cookies are small text based information packets stored by the web based browsers (such as Chrome, Internet Explorer, Firefox or any other web based browser) on user computer. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers. 

### Google Analytics Cookie

Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on user computers. IP-Tracker.org use Google Analytics to analyse and collect information how do you use IP-Tracker.org. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. IP-Tracker.org don't collect or store your personal information (for example your name or physical address) so information from Google Analytics can't be used to identify who you are. 

We don't allow Google to use or share our analytics data. 

To opt out Google Analytics Cookie visit [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

### Privacy Policy For Third party advertisements on IP-Tracker.org (DoubleClick DART Cookie)

We use third party advertisement (only from Google Adsense) on IP-Tracker.org to support our site: 

  * Third party vendor, as Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Google's use of DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to IP-Tracker.org and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick DART cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting - <https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. If you would like to opt-out your preference permanently then you can use browser plugin which can permanently opt out of the DoubleClick cookie - <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin> Or you can set your browser to refuse cookies. 

Unless you have set your browser to refuse cookies, the next time you visit a website running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

If you do not want to opt out then please visit [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/) to edit the preferences

IP-Tracker.org reserve the right to make changes to its Privacy Policy at any time. So please review this page frequently for any changes in our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our website or our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.ip-tracker.org/contact.php). 

Advertisements

* * *
